Welcome to our channel Stock Market In
Posters, I hope you all are here, so
friends, here I am going to talk about
ICICI Lombard which has
presented its quarterly numbers,
let's see the company's numbers,
how are the numbers and
what should be our decision regarding the company in the coming time, so
first of all let's see the
company's numbers here, how are the numbers given,
Pradyot has given the British Rulers
in the next, so you will see the company's numbers here, first of all we will
talk about the total income of the company, then we are going to talk about the premium of the company, first of all let's see the
total income, there should be a proper
visual of it, so here are the life numbers of
last year, life numbers of share
and why the phone numbers of last year, that means,
potter in quarter senior and junior, you will get
to see here, see the
poison peer weight from the company last year, which has increased,
then from the next point,
Zuha means that the revenue of the company is seen increasing in senior and junior,
Dr.
Friday, Flex from here 1000, so
quarter liquid is being seen in  The
company's revenue is increasing, but quite early
on, the company's revenue seems to be decreasing.
If we talk about the company, the
total income of the company is a
little less. The company's premium comes from selling the mains, from the
premium of the company's insurance companies,
so the company's
revenue increases further. If you look at the company last year,
this means the net premium was
5000 rupees, which has
increased to more than 250 rupees this time because it is
bigger than the previous quarter. The revenue is
also quite high and if we
talk about the
company's interest in that business, the
company's revenue is
increasing a bit. And I also want to know these
small things of the company which many people ignore,
which we need to know. So,
total, but before that, the company is subscribing to its business.
Last
year, the company
subscribed, which means the company is
reducing the working expenses in the business, which is a good
signal, so the company is
reducing the expenses for the product. If we talk about
quarter to quarter, but talking about quarter to quarter, you
can see that  It looks quite good here in Italy,
you will
definitely see the expense cup here below, I mentioned it as an edit above,
but the free leg 7700 and the
relax 60 this time, which means clearly the expenses have
reduced, if we talk about the quarter, the
expenses of the Zouk Water Lily companies have reduced, so
in both these liquid li, the company has set its expenses
very strongly here, so the
company is able to generate profit,
that a little milk was added, no problem, let's
talk about profit after tax,
how much is the company generating, so friends, what
I have done is amazing, the company will present the result
9000, which means that I will write it on it, did not
30 1994
sure generate cars, which this time the business is
3403, which means it is amazing, here the company has
increased the revenue, net company income, if we
talk about the last quarter, there is
water treatment till f-18, so improvement
means 34 thousand 903 company should generate its
business  The company has presented amazing results, if we
talk about it here then let's
talk about it from here, it is being seen that it is a
very wonderful company, the company is going to
see amazing growth, so you can
definitely do it, it is a general insurance company and a
very good company, if we talk about it the company is
good, there is
no need to be afraid, so friends I hope you
liked the video, then like and
subscribe
Pimple got the information that today the
numbers of all the companies like Safed Musli Company Garam-Up will be
seen in the video section,
whether it is Chur or it is liked by you,
all the numbers of Ambuja Cement will be
seen in the video section, Politics
of India, so we will meet in the next video, till then
bye-bye take care